const level19questions =[
     
{
    question: "8 x 9 - 1 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["70", "72", "55", "86"],
    answer: "72",
},
{
    question: "6 + 9 - 9 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["13", "9", "6", "10"],
    answer: "6",
},
{
    question: "3 + 10 x 4 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["11", "21", "33", "27"],
    answer: "33",
},
{
    question: "7 - 10 + 4 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["5", "-1", "1", "7"],
    answer: "-1",
},
{
    question: "1 x 1 + 4 - 3 = ?",
    options: ["27", "62", "2", "26"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "1 + 3 x 7 - 2 = ?",
    options: ["20", "27", "36", "43"],
    answer: "20",
},
{
    question: "6 x 3 + 8 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["21", "38", "3", "14"],
    answer: "21",
},
{
    question: "6 + 4 / 4 - 1 = ?",
    options: ["1", "2", "-4", "6"],
    answer: "-4",
},
{
    question: "6 x 3 + 7 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["38", "43", "20", "22"],
    answer: "20",
},
{
    question: "4 + 7 / 7 - 4 = ?",
    options: ["7", "4", "9", "1"],
    answer: "1",
},

{
    question: "2 - 10 x 2 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["-41", "-8", "-56", "-12"],
    answer: "-8"
},
{
    question: "5 + 4 - 10 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["9", "17", "15", "4"],
    answer: "9"
},
{
    question: "6 x 10 - 9 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["61", "57", "38", "4"],
    answer: "57"
},
{
    question: "10 + 3 - 7 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["-29", "-13", "-43", "-38"],
    answer: "-43"
},
{
    question: "9 x 9 + 7 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["14", "83", "0", "53"],
    answer: "83"
},
{
    question: "10 + 9 - 3 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["12", "1", "18", "11"],
    answer: "12"
},
{
    question: "2 - 4 x 6 + 8 = ?",
    options: ["-14", "-81", "-3", "-28"],
    answer: "-14"
},
{
    question: "1 - 10 x 10 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["-23", "-95", "-1", "-39"],
    answer: "-95"
},
{
    question: "4 x 3 + 9 - 2 = ?",
    options: ["19", "9", "47", "48"],
    answer: "19"
},
{
    question: "3 + 9 - 9 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["-78", "-13", "-18", "8"],
    answer: "-78"
},
{
    question: "2 - 2 + 8 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["80", "39", "42", "21"],
    answer: "80"
},
{
    question: "4 - 2 x 8 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["-30", "10", "-7", "-52"],
    answer: "-7"
},
{
    question: "3 - 9 x 6 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["-46", "-26", "-4", "6"],
    answer: "-46"
},
{
    question: "5 + 10 x 7 - 1 = ?",
    options: ["74", "57", "-3", "64"],
    answer: "74"
},
{
    question: "5 + 9 / 9 - 6 = ?",
    options: ["3", "0", "2", "10"],
    answer: "0"
},
{
    question: "10 + 3 / 3 - 6 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "8", "5", "2"],
    answer: "-3"
},
{
    question: "4 - 8 x 6 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["-24", "-34", "-40", "-31"],
    answer: "-40"
},
{
    question: "1 - 3 x 1 + 9 = ?",
    options: ["7", "-30", "-10", "-31"],
    answer: "7"
},
{
    question: "2 - 1 + 8 / 4 = ?",
    options: ["9", "6", "10", "3"],
    answer: "3"
},
{
    question: "9 + 10 x 9 - 6 = ?",
    options: ["89", "93", "75", "10"],
    answer: "93"
},
{
    question: "6 x 2 - 3 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["14", "31", "85", "39"],
    answer: "14"
},
{
    question: "8 x 6 - 9 + 2 = ?",
    options: ["41", "38", "56", "26"],
    answer: "41"
},
{
    question: "8 / 2 - 3 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["1", "2", "6", "-4"],
    answer: "1"
},
{
    question: "3 - 10 + 8 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["4", "7", "-1", "-3"],
    answer: "7"
},
{
    question: "6 - 2 + 9 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["35", "67", "29", "10"],
    answer: "67"
},

{
    question: "2 - 7 x 1 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["-5", "-70", "0", "-18"],
    answer: "0",
},
{
    question: "6 + 9 - 9 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["7", "3", "6", "12"],
    answer: "7",
},
{
    question: "1 + 2 x 3 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["40", "2", "18", "27"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "3 - 3 + 10 / 10 = ?",
    options: ["12", "4", "1", "8"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "4 - 4 x 2 + 3 = ?",
    options: ["0", "-1", "-27", "1"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "3 + 1 - 2 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["3", "12", "11", "6"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "9 x 3 + 7 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["15", "22", "-4", "24"],
    answer: "24",
},
{
    question: "7 / 1 - 2 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["0", "7", "9", "-4"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "6 - 7 + 8 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["73", "16", "23", "17"],
    answer: "23",
},
{
    question: "6 - 3 x 9 + 3 = ?",
    options: ["-21", "-11", "-7", "-18"],
    answer: "-21",
},
{
    question: "9 - 9 / 3 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["9", "11", "1", "12"],
    answer: "11",
},
{
    question: "7 - 9 x 10 + 9 = ?",
    options: ["-54", "-24", "-1", "-74"],
    answer: "-74",
},
{
    question: "6 - 1 + 9 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["57", "48", "1", "95"],
    answer: "57",
},
{
    question: "3 - 9 / 3 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["2", "4", "10", "-3"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "2 / 2 - 10 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["2", "3", "-4", "1"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "2 + 2 - 3 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["8", "9", "1", "11"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "6 + 9 - 8 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["-13", "-65", "2", "15"],
    answer: "-65",
},
{
    question: "8 + 8 x 6 - 9 = ?",
    options: ["77", "47", "10", "72"],
    answer: "47",
},
{
    question: "10 / 2 - 3 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["-4", "1", "5", "6"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "6 / 6 - 10 + 7 = ?",
    options: ["7", "15", "-2", "17"],
    answer: "15",
},
{
    question: "4 - 3 + 7 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["57", "48", "41", "36"],
    answer: "36",
},
{
    question: "8 x 7 - 3 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["72", "17", "29", "59"],
    answer: "72",
},
{
    question: "9 + 4 - 4 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["5", "11", "-4", "-76"],
    answer: "5",
},
{
    question: "2 - 2 + 9 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["-4", "11", "3", "-6"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "1 x 1 + 6 - 8 = ?",
    options: ["-1", "59", "39", "8"],
    answer: "-1",
},

{
    question: "3 + 2 x 5 - 1 = ?",
    options: ["31", "8", "53", "12"],
    answer: "12",
},
{
    question: "8 / 1 - 9 + 10 = ?",
    options: ["1", "8", "9", "5"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "1 + 3 - 3 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["7", "1", "9", "10"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "3 - 5 + 6 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["7", "4", "0", "8"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "6 + 9 - 4 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["12", "9", "16", "13"],
    answer: "13",
},
{
    question: "4 / 2 - 9 + 10 = ?",
    options: ["5", "-8", "3", "2"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "7 / 7 - 4 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["2", "-1", "9", "5"],
    answer: "5",
},
{
    question: "4 - 2 / 1 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["9", "0", "3", "7"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "9 - 7 / 7 + 8 = ?",
    options: ["6", "9", "16", "7"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "10 + 6 - 5 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["10", "-29", "-8", "-18"],
    answer: "-29",
},
{
    question: "5 - 7 + 10 / 10 = ?",
    options: ["6", "8", "2", "-1"],
    answer: "-1",
},
{
    question: "9 + 6 - 10 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["13", "8", "2", "5"],
    answer: "5",
},
{
    question: "6 - 9 + 6 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["26", "1", "30", "3"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "4 x 4 - 8 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["9", "37", "4", "70"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "5 - 3 + 6 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["68", "67", "8", "23"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "6 + 1 x 5 - 2 = ?",
    options: ["9", "16", "18", "21"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "10 x 1 - 10 + 3 = ?",
    options: ["9", "3", "64", "18"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "2 x 9 + 1 - 1 = ?",
    options: ["1", "60", "18", "-1"],
    answer: "18",
},
{
    question: "2 - 7 + 4 / 4 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "4", "-4", "7"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "6 + 6 x 1 - 4 = ?",
    options: ["17", "28", "63", "8"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "1 - 7 / 7 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["11", "7", "6", "3"],
    answer: "6",
},
{
    question: "6 + 6 - 9 / 9 = ?",
    options: ["12", "14", "15", "11"],
    answer: "12",
},
{
    question: "5 x 9 - 3 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["48", "20", "40", "17"],
    answer: "48",
},
{
    question: "6 + 4 / 2 - 3 = ?",
    options: ["-2", "5", "6", "0"],
    answer: "5",
},
{
    question: "3 x 5 - 9 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["26", "8", "10", "-1"],
    answer: "10",
},

{
    question: "2 + 8 - 6 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["-5", "-14", "-24", "-2"],
    answer: "-2",
},
{
    question: "10 - 4 + 6 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["8", "5", "-3", "4"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "1 - 4 x 3 + 5 = ?",
    options: ["-4", "-6", "8", "11"],
    answer: "-6",
},
{
    question: " 7 + 3 x 4 - 3 = ?",
    options: ["25", "16", "15", "3"],
    answer: "16",
},
{
    question: "9 - 7 + 2 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["16", "30", "12", "26"],
    answer: "12",
},
{
    question: "7 + 7 / 1 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["5", "-2", "4", "6"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "7 + 10 / 2 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "4", "2", "5"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "10 - 7 / 7 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["12", "7", "1", "13"],
    answer: "7",
},
{
    question: "7 / 1 - 9 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["0", "1", "10", "2"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "1 - 2 + 9 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["28", "7", "5", "8"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "6 / 3 + 7 - 4 = ?",
    options: ["5", "4", "13", "6"],
    answer: "5",
},
{
    question: "3 / 1 - 2 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["2", "0", "14", "8"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "9 - 5 + 6 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["26", "15", "58", "23"],
    answer: "58",
},
{
    question: "7 + 1 / 1 - 6 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "-4", "7", "2"],
    answer: "-4",
},
{
    question: "10 / 1 - 7 + 1 = ?",
    options: ["9", "1", "4", "-6"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "4 x 6 + 6 - 9 = ?",
    options: ["14", "21", "17", "27"],
    answer: "17",
},
{
    question: "10 + 1 - 9 / 9 = ?",
    options: ["10", "17", "8", "4"],
    answer: "10",
},
{
    question: "4 + 9 / 3 - 1 = ?",
    options: ["1", "8", "6", "-2"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "6 / 2 - 3 + 7 = ?",
    options: ["4", "-1", "7", "-2"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "3 + 10 - 10 / 5 = ?",
    options: ["10", "11", "6", "14"],
    answer: "6",
},
{
    question: "1 + 1 - 4 / 4 = ?",
    options: ["1", "5", "13", "15"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "5 - 9 + 1 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["0", "11", "59", "76"],
    answer: "0",
},
{
question: "4 - 6 + 4 / 4 = ?",
options: ["-1", "5", "4", "14"],
answer: "4",
},
{
question: "5 x 6 - 3 + 1 = ?",
options: ["81", "33", "35", "28"],
answer: "28",
},
{
question: "5 - 8 x 10 + 8 = ?",
options: ["-38", "-67", "-34", "-2"],
answer: "-67",
},
];
export default level19questions;